Guide to the American Federation of Television and Radio Artists (AFTRA) National Office Records WAG.281
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series VIII: Charges, Claims, and Arbitrations
  - AFTRA [Chicago Local] vs Globe Broadcasting Co., Postponed Indefinitely, 1986 (Box 151, Folder 16)
  - AFTRA vs Golden West Broadcasting Corp., 1975 (Box 151, Folder 17)
  - AFTRA [Los Angeles Local] vs Gotch, Lee: Disciplinary Proceedings, 1961 (Box 151, Folder 18)
  - AFTRA vs International Teleview, Inc. re: Clive Barnes, Charles Nelson Reilly, Vincent Sardi, 1982 (Box 151, Folder 19)
  - AFTRA vs KDFW, 1987-1989 (Box 151, Folder 20)
  - AFTRA [Tri-State Local] vs Kline, Vicki, 1989-1990 (Box 151, Folder 21)
  - AFTRA [Tri-State Local] vs Kline, Vicki, 1991 (Box 151, Folder 22)
  - AFTRA vs KTBC-TV (also Times Mirror Broadcasting), 1981-1982 (Box 151, Folder 23)
  - AFTRA [Cleveland Local] vs Marcus Advertising Company, 1985 (Box 151, Folder 24)
  - AFTRA vs National Association of Broadcasters (NAB) re: Commercials in Children's Programming, 1971 (Box 151, Folder 25)
  - AFTRA vs National Association of Broadcasters re: Commercials in Children's Programming, 1972 (Box 151, Folder 26)
  - AFTRA vs National Association of Broadcasters re: Commercials in Children's Programming, Jan 1973-Apr 1973 (Box 151, Folder 27)
  - AFTRA vs National Association of Broadcasters re: Commercials in Children's Programming, May 1973-Aug 1973 (Box 151, Folder 28)
  - AFTRA vs National Association of Broadcasters re: Commercials in Children's Programming, 1974-1975 (Box 151, Folder 29)
  - AFTRA vs NBC re: Mileage for Network Newsmen in Washington, DC, 1971 (Box 151, Folder 30)
  - AFTRA vs NBC (Staff Newspersons), 1984-1987 (Box 151, Folder 31)
  - AFTRA vs NPR, 1976 (Box 151, Folder 32)
  - AFTRA [Cleveland Local] vs Nitty Gritty Advertising and Walter Masky, 1984 (Box 151, Folder 33)
  - AFTRA vs Palmer, Shelton Leigh Co. re: Payment of Manna, 1987-1988 (Box 151, Folder 34)
  - AFTRA vs PGHM Productions, Inc., 1993 (Box 151, Folder 35)
  - AFTRA [Washington Local] vs Pilgrim Film Services: Unfair Labor Practice Charge, 1961 (Box 151, Folder 36)
  - AFTRA [Detroit Local] vs Radio Station WFDF re: David Leyton, 1982 (Box 151, Folder 37)
  - AFTRA vs Sagittarius Broadcasting Corp. (WXRK/Howard Stern Case), 1989-1991 (Box 151, Folder 38)
  - AFTRA vs Scepter Records, Inc., 1975 (Box 151, Folder 39)
  - AFTRA vs Scott, Willard (as NBC), 1980 (Box 151, Folder 40)
  - AFTRA vs Spanish International Communication Corp., 1979 (Box 151, Folder 41)
  - AFTRA vs Talent and Residuals, Inc., 1972, 1976-1977 (Box 151, Folder 42)
  - AFTRA vs Trans-Tel Corporation and Spanish International Communication Corp., 1979 (Box 151, Folder 43)
  - AFTRA vs WABC-TV re: Zaret, Eli and Health & Retirement Contributions, 1988 (Box 151, Folder 44)
  - AFTRA vs WCCO, 1987 (Box 151, Folder 45)
  - AFTRA vs WCIN-AM (Cincinnati) re: Mike Davis Demotion (includes on-going memos from AFTRA representative Fernanda Crudo), 1983-1986 (Box 151, Folder 46)
  - AFTRA vs WDIV and Mike Wendland, 1982, 1987 (Box 151, Folder 47)
  - AFTRA vs Wenzel, William Settlement, Sep 1987 (Box 151, Folder 48)
  - AFTRA [Los Angeles Local] vs Westinghouse Broadcasting Co. (Station KFWB) re: Frank Gonzalez, 1981 (Box 151, Folder 49)
  - AFTRA [Pittsburgh Local] vs Westinghouse Broadcasting Co./KKDA-TV, 1983 (Box 151, Folder 50)
  - AFTRA [New York Local] vs Westinghouse Broadcasting Co. re: WINS Radio, 1966 (Box 151, Folder 51)
  - AFTRA vs WIIC-TV (Pittsburgh, PA) re: Beverly Byer Vacation Benefits, 1980 (Box 151, Folder 52)
  - American Guild of Variety Artists (AGVA) and Penny Singleton vs The Associated Actors and Artistes of America (4As): Correspondence and Related Cases and Materials, 1972-1974 (Box 151, Folder 53)
  - American Guild of Variety Artists and Penny Singleton vs The Associated Actors and Artistes of America: Legal Documents, 1972 (Box 151, Folder 54)
  - American Guild of Variety Artists and Penny Singleton vs The Associated Actors and Artistes of America: Legal Documents, 1973 (Box 151, Folder 55)
  - American Guild of Variety Artists and Penny Singleton vs The Associated Actors and Artistes of America: Meeting Minutes, 4As, 1971 (Box 151, Folder 56)
  - American Guild of Variety Artists and Penny Singleton vs The Associated Actors and Artistes of America: Meeting Minutes, 4As, 1972 (Box 151, Folder 57)
  - The Associated Actors and Artistes of America vs American Guild of Variety Artists, Jan 1972-Mar 1972 (Box 152, Folder 1)
  - The Associated Actors and Artistes of America vs American Guild of Variety Artists, May 1972 (Box 152, Folder 2)
  - The Associated Actors and Artistes of America vs American Guild of Variety Artists, Jun 1972-Jul 1972 (Box 152, Folder 3)
  - Authorizations Binder: Atlanta to Detroit, 1979-1986 (Box 152, Folder 4)
  - Authorizations Binder: Fresno to San Diego, 1980-1986 (Box 152, Folder 5)
  - Authorizations Binder: San Francisco to Washington/Baltimore, 1980-1986 (Box 152, Folder 6)
  - Barr, Richard vs The Dramatists Guild, et al., Aug 1982 (Box 152, Folder 7)
  - [AFTRA vs] Batten, Barton, Durstine & Osborn (BBD&D) re: Delta and Dodge Commercials, 1977-1981 (Box 152, Folder 8)
  - [AFTRA vs] Batten, Barton, Durstine & Osborn re: Support Material from Locals, 1980 (Box 152, Folder 9)
  - Batten, Barton, Durstine & Osborn vs AFTRA re: Television Commercials Contract, 1980 (Box 152, Folder 10)
  - Breslin, Jimmy vs Woody Fraser Productions, Inc., 1987 (Box 152, Folder 11)
  - Brown, Robert and Ryan's Hope, Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 152, Folder 12)
  - Buckley, William F. and National Review, Inc. vs AFTRA, Jan 1971-Feb 1971 (Box 152, Folder 13)
  - Buckley, William F. and National Review, Inc. vs AFTRA, Mar 1971-Apr 1971 (Box 152, Folder 14)
  - Buckley, William F. and National Review, Inc. vs AFTRA, May 1971-Jun 1971 (Box 152, Folder 15)
  - Buckley, William F. and National Review, Inc. vs AFTRA, Jul 1971 (Box 152, Folder 16)
  - Buckley, William F. and National Review, Inc. vs AFTRA, Sep 1971 (Box 152, Folder 17)
  - Buckley, William F. and National Review, Inc. vs AFTRA [M. Stanton Evans vs AFTRA], Sep 1971 (Box 152, Folder 18)
  - Buckley, William F. and National Review, Inc. vs AFTRA, Oct 1971 (Box 152, Folder 19)
  - Buckley, William F. and National Review, Inc. vs AFTRA, Nov 1971-Dec 1971 (Box 152, Folder 20)
  - Buckley, William F. and National Review, Inc. vs AFTRA, Jan 1972-Feb 1972 (Box 152, Folder 21)
  - Buckley, William F. and National Review, Inc. vs AFTRA, Mar 1972 (Box 152, Folder 22)
  - Buckley, William F. and National Review, Inc. vs AFTRA, Apr 1972 (Box 152, Folder 23)
  - Buckley, William F. and National Review, Inc. vs AFTRA, May 1972 (Box 152, Folder 24)
  - Buckley, William F. and National Review, Inc. vs AFTRA, Jun 1972 (Box 152, Folder 25)
  - Buckley, William F. and National Review, Inc. vs AFTRA, Jul 1972 (Box 152, Folder 26)
  - Buckley, William F. and National Review, Inc. vs AFTRA, Sep 1972-Nov 1972 (Box 152, Folder 27)
  - Buckley, William F. and National Review, Inc. vs AFTRA, Jan 1973-Feb 1973 (Box 152, Folder 28)
  - Buckley, William F. and National Review, Inc. vs AFTRA [Joint Appendix], Feb 1973 (Box 153, Folder 1)
  - Buckley, William F. and National Review, Inc. vs AFTRA, May 1973-Aug 1973 (Box 153, Folder 2)
  - Buckley, William F. and National Review, Inc. vs AFTRA, Sep 1973 (Box 153, Folder 3)
  - Buckley, William F. and National Review, Inc. vs AFTRA, Oct 1973 (Box 153, Folder 4)
  - Buckley, William F. and National Review, Inc. vs AFTRA [Professor Alexander Bickel Report and Related Correspondence], 1973-1975 (Box 153, Folder 5)
  - Buckley, William F. and National Review, Inc. vs AFTRA, Jan 1974-Apr 1974 (Box 153, Folder 6)
  - Buckley, William F. and National Review, Inc. vs AFTRA, May 1974-Jun 1974 (Box 153, Folder 7)
  - Buckley, William F. and National Review, Inc. vs AFTRA, Jul 1974-Aug 1974 (Box 153, Folder 8)
  - Buckley, William F. and National Review, Inc. vs AFTRA, Oct 1974-Dec 1974 (Box 153, Folder 9)
  - Buckley, William F. and National Review, Inc. vs AFTRA, Jan 1975-Apr 1975 (Box 153, Folder 10)
  - Buckley, William F. and National Review, Inc. vs AFTRA, May 1975-Jun 1975 (Box 153, Folder 11)
  - Buckley, William F. and National Review, Inc. vs AFTRA, Oct 1975-Nov 1975 (Box 153, Folder 12)
  - Buckley, William F. and National Review, Inc. vs AFTRA, Dec 1975 (Box 153, Folder 13)
  - Buckley, William F. and National Review, Inc. vs AFTRA, Jan 1976-Apr 1976 (Box 153, Folder 14)
  - Buckley, William F. and National Review, Inc. vs AFTRA, May 1976-Sep 1976 (Box 153, Folder 15)
  - Buckley, William F. and National Review, Inc. vs AFTRA, 1977-1978 (Box 153, Folder 16)
  - Buckley, William F. and National Review, Inc. vs AFTRA [Notice to Signatories Post Settlement], 1978 (Box 153, Folder 17)
  - Buffalo Broadcasting Co., Inc. vs AFTRA re: Alleged Breach of Agreement, Compensation of Performers, 1983 (Box 153, Folder 18)
  - Callicut Productions vs Kenny Rogers, Dottie West, Oak Ridge Boys, AFTRA, 1982 (Box 153, Folder 19)
  - Capital Cities Broadcasting Corporation [WROW-AM-FM] vs AFTRA re: Announcer Fees, 1971, 1974 (Box 153, Folder 20)
  - Capital Cities Communications, Inc. vs AFTRA re: Michael Fierberg, 1983 (Box 153, Folder 21)
  - Coding of Television Commercials and Programs: International Digisonics, Correspondence and Related Material, 1969 (Box 153, Folder 22)
  - Coding of Television: International Digisonics, Correspondence and Related Material, 1970-1971 (Box 153, Folder 23)
  - Coding of Television: International Digisonics, Correspondence and Related Material, 1972 (Box 153, Folder 24)
  - Coding of Television: International Digisonics, Federal Communication Commission, 1972 (Box 153, Folder 25)
  - CBS vs William Baldwin, as President, and Mel Brandt, as Treasurer, of AFTRA re: AFTRA Support of IBEW Strike, Correspondence and Related Material, 1972 (Box 153, Folder 26)
  - CBS vs Baldwin: Correspondence, Legal Documents and Related Material, 1973 (Box 153, Folder 27)
  - CBS vs William Baldwin, as President, and Mel Brandt, as Treasurer, of AFTRA re: AFTRA Support of IBEW Strike: Exhibits, 1972 (Box 153, Folder 28)
  - CBS vs William Baldwin, as President, and Mel Brandt, as Treasurer, of AFTRA re: AFTRA Support of IBEW Strike: Legal Documents, 1972 (Box 154, Folder 1)
  - CBS vs Baldwin: Press Clippings, 1972-1973 (Box 154, Folder 2)
  - CBS Records, Inc. vs AFTRA re: "Of Thee I Sing" and "Let 'Em Eat Cake" at BAM, 1988 (Box 154, Folder 3)
  - CBS (WBBM) vs AFTRA, Aug 1985, May 1987 (Box 154, Folder 4)
  - Columbia Pictures Television vs AFTRA re: Reducing Guarantees for "The Young and the Restless", 1986 (Box 154, Folder 5)
  - Community Antenna Television (CATV) Systems, 1965-1968 (Box 154, Folder 6)
  - Community Antenna Television Systems, Mar 1970-Feb 1971 (Box 154, Folder 7)
  - Costa, Mary (as AFTRA) vs Walt Disney Company, Sep 1990-Oct 1990 (Box 154, Folder 8)
  - Dalheim, Edward D, et al. vs KDFW-TV, Dec 1990 (Box 154, Folder 9)
  - Department of Labor, Collective Bargaining Statements, 1970 (Box 154, Folder 10)
  - Disciplinary Proceeding Procedures, 1956, 1960 (Box 154, Folder 11)
  - The Disney Channel, 1983-1984, 1991 (Box 154, Folder 12)
  - Domestic Replay Fees, 1974 (Box 154, Folder 13)
  - Federal Mediation and Conciliation Service: Correspondence, 1976-1985 (Box 154, Folder 14)
  - Financial Core: Correspondence, 1985 (Box 154, Folder 15)
  - Fraser, Woody Productions vs Jimmy Breslin, 1987 (Box 154, Folder 16)
  - Gannett, Guy Broadcasting Services Arbitration vs AFTRA Locals in Boston, Chicago and St. Louis, 1981-1983 (Box 154, Folder 17)
  - General, 1975-1990 (Box 154, Folder 18)
  - Glass, Katherine vs ABC, 1978 (Box 154, Folder 19)
  - Gleason Entertainment and Jackie Gleason: Demand for Payment re: Use of Old Honeymooners Shows, Jan 1985-Apr 1985 (Box 154, Folder 20)
  - Gleason Entertainment and Jackie Gleason: Demand for Payment re: Use of Old Honeymooners Shows, May 1985-Apr 1986 (Box 154, Folder 21)
  - Goldstein, Donald et al. vs State of California re: Music Piracy, 1971-1973 (Box 154, Folder 22)
  - Granada TV Rental Ltd. vs Rickie Ricardo Entertainment Inc., 1986 (Box 154, Folder 23)
  - Group Legal Services: Correspondence, 1972 (Box 154, Folder 24)
  - Hearst Corporation-WISN Division vs AFTRA [Chicago Local], 1987 (Box 154, Folder 25)
  - Hennepin Broadcasting Associates vs AFTRA [Twin Cities Local], 1975-1976 (Box 154, Folder 26)
  - Holiday Radio, Inc. vs AFTRA, et al., Jan 1982-Jul 1982 (Box 154, Folder 27)
  - Holiday Radio, Inc. vs AFTRA, et al., Aug 1982-Dec 1982 (Box 154, Folder 28)
  - Holiday Radio, Inc. vs AFTRA, et al., 1983 (Box 154, Folder 29)
  - Hurley, James re: Disciplinary Action Filed by Erie Chapter, 1953 (Box 154, Folder 30)
  - Jaffe, Henry Letter re: Constitutional Amendment Concerning Disciplinary Hearings, 1943 (Box 154, Folder 31)
  - James, Joni and Toni Acquiviva vs Associated Booking Corp. et al., 1977 (Box 154, Folder 32)
  - Jay-Bar Industries and Jackie Barnett vs AFTRA, 1977-1979 (Box 154, Folder 33)
  - Joint Policy Committee on Broadcast Talent-Union Relationships re: Advertising Agencies Signing Letters of Adherence, 1964-1965 (Box 154, Folder 34)
  - Jordan, Joanne Correspondence re: Raymond Spector Co, Inc. Payments, 1954-1959 (Box 154, Folder 35)
  - KPIX-TV Group W, Westinghouse Broadcasting and Cable, Inc. vs AFTRA [San Francisco Local] re: Pension and Welfare Contributions, 1983 (Box 154, Folder 36)
  - LK [Larry Kane] Productions vs AFTRA and AFTRA vs LK Productions: Consolidarity Cases, 1972-1973 (Box 154, Folder 37)
  - LK Productions vs AFTRA, Dallas-Ft Worth Local: Correspondence and Related Material, 1972-1973 (Box 154, Folder 38)
  - LK Productions vs AFTRA, Dallas-Ft Worth Local: Correspondence and Related Material, 1975-1976 (Box 154, Folder 39)
  - LK Productions vs AFTRA, Dallas-Ft Worth Local: Correspondence and Related Material, 1977-1978 (Box 154, Folder 40)
  - LK Productions vs AFTRA, Dallas-Ft Worth Local: Exhibits, 1973 (Box 154, Folder 41)
  - LK Productions vs AFTRA, Dallas-Ft Worth Local: Legal Documents, US District Court Civil Action, 1976-1977 (Box 155, Folder 1)
  - LK Productions vs AFTRA, Dallas-Ft Worth Local: Legal Documents, US District Court Civil Action, 1978-1980 (Box 155, Folder 2)
  - LK Productions vs AFTRA, Dallas-Ft Worth Local: National Board Minutes and Related Material, 1972-1973 (Box 155, Folder 3)
  - LK Productions vs AFTRA, Dallas-Ft Worth Local: NLRB Proceedings Transcript Vol. I, Jan 8, 1973 (Box 155, Folder 4)
  - LK Productions vs AFTRA, Dallas-Ft Worth Local: NLRB Proceedings Transcript Vol. II, Jan 9, 1973 (Box 155, Folder 5)
  - Lewis, Fulton III vs AFTRA: Legal Documents and Related Correspondence, 1971 (Box 155, Folder 6)
  - Lewis, Fulton III vs AFTRA: Legal Documents and Related Correspondence, Jan 1972 (Box 155, Folder 7)
  - Lewis, Fulton III vs AFTRA: Legal Documents and Related Correspondence, Feb 1972-Jun 1974 (Box 155, Folder 8)
  - Lewis, Fulton III vs AFTRA: New York Supreme Court Appellate Division Briefs, 1972 (Box 155, Folder 9)
  - Marsh, Media of El Paso vs AFTRA, 1984 (Box 155, Folder 10)
  - Mason, Paul Bailey: Correspondence Regarding Dismissal, 1971-1972 (Box 155, Folder 11)
  - Mason, Paul Bailey: Correspondence Regarding Dismissal, 1973 (Box 155, Folder 12)
  - McIlvaine, Red: Disciplinary Charges, 1963 (Box 155, Folder 13)
  - Medford, Kay vs John Frederic Hart re: Unpaid Salary, 1978-1981 (Box 155, Folder 14)
  - Meredith Corporation: Refusal to Bargain Charge, 1979 (Box 155, Folder 15)
  - Metacom Co. vs American Forces Radio and Television Service, 1978 (Box 155, Folder 16)
  - Metromedia, Inc. vs Trophy, Productions, et al. re: Judy Garland Shows, 1974-1975, 1979 (Box 155, Folder 17)
  - Miller, Mitch vs CBS, 1979 (Box 155, Folder 18)
  - Monett Media, Inc. to be Placed on Unfair List, 1977-1978 (Box 155, Folder 19)
  - Montgomery, Robert vs Joanne Dru and George Foley vs Paul Lukas, 1953-1954 (Box 155, Folder 20)
  - Morgan, Ray Correspondence re: Charges of Working for a Non-Signatory, 1972-1973 (Box 155, Folder 21)
  - Nash Communications Corp. d/b/a WILD-AM vs AFTRA [Boston Local], 1989 (Box 155, Folder 22)
  - National Labor Relation's Board (NLRB) Hearings re: Tape Includes BBD&O vs AFTRA, 1958 (Box 155, Folder 23)
  - Odyssey Productions, Inc. vs AFTRA, Jun 21, 1976 (Box 155, Folder 24)
  - Odyssey Productions, Inc. vs AFTRA, Aug 1976-Mar 1978 (Box 155, Folder 25)
  - Office & Professional Employees International Union (OPEI) Local 153 vs AFTRA re: Discharge of Agnes Simon, 1987-1988 (Box 155, Folder 26)
  - Office & Professional Employees International Union (OPEI) Local 153 vs AFTRA re: Wage Increases, 1987-1988 (Box 155, Folder 27)
  - Park, Junius Andrew and AFTRA vs ABC, 1975 (Box 155, Folder 28)
  - Paulsen, Patrick vs FCC, 1972 (Box 155, Folder 29)
  - Payne, Virginia and League of New York Theatres, Correspondence, 1963 (Box 155, Folder 30)
  - "Proving Your Arbitration Case" by Boaz Siegel, 1977 (Box 155, Folder 31)
  - Radel, Robert N. (as AFTRA) vs CBS, Jun 1977 (Box 155, Folder 32)
  - RCR Productions, Inc. (as AFTRA) vs NLRB re: Jason York, 1960 (Box 155, Folder 33)
  - Redgrave, Vanessa vs Boston Symphony Orchestra, Inc., 1982-1985 (Box 155, Folder 34)
  - Reich, Adell and Crost Arbitration and Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 155, Folder 35)
  - Reich, Adell and Crost Arbitration and Correspondence, 1987-1992 (Box 155, Folder 36)
  - Reimel, Theodore L., Jr. t/a T.L. Reimel Advertising vs AFTRA and American Arbitration Association, 1974 (Box 155, Folder 37)
  - Reno's: A Reunion for AIDS, 1988 (Box 155, Folder 38)
  - Right to Work Cases, 1975-1976 (Box 156, Folder 1)
  - RKO-General vs AFTRA, 1977 (Box 156, Folder 2)
  - RKO-General Broadcasting, Inc. Correspondence and Related Material (incl. Case Against FCC et al.), 1978-1986 (Box 156, Folder 3)
  - Rosenfeld, Alvin re: NBC Washington, D.C. Contract, 1971-1976 (Box 156, Folder 4)
  - Sagittarius Broadcasting Corp., Employment Agreements (WXRK), 1989 (Box 156, Folder 5)
  - Santos, Larry vs ABC: Claim for Services, Dec 1988-May 1989 (Box 156, Folder 6)
  - Santos, Larry vs ABC, Nov 1989-Dec 1989 (Box 156, Folder 7)
  - Santos, Larry vs ABC, Jan 1990 (Box 156, Folder 8)
  - Saxton Communications Group, Ltd. Bankruptcy (AFTRA a Creditor), 1987 (Box 156, Folder 9)
  - Scamardella, Roseann vs ABC, 1985 (Box 156, Folder 10)
  - Schultz, Marilyn for WC=EO Women at NBC vs NBC et al. re: Unlawful Discrimination, 1975 (Box 156, Folder 11)
  - Shapiro, Kelly, Memos, Appeals, Correspondence and Related Material, 1986-1987 (Box 156, Folder 12)
  - Sheridan Broadcasting Corp., Radio Station WAMO-FM vs AFTRA [Pittsburgh Local] re: Ms. Jackie A. Johnson, 1984 (Box 156, Folder 13)
  - Sherwood, Don: Correspondence re: Possible NBC Arbitration, 1957 (Box 156, Folder 14)
  - [Claims Against] Sorrentino, Mark, Correspondence and Related Material, 1961 (Box 156, Folder 15)
  - Spanish International Network vs AFTRA re: Spanish Language Commercials, 1975, 1979 (Box 156, Folder 16)
  - Spero, Herman Productions, Inc vs AFTRA, 1971-1974 (Box 156, Folder 17)
  - State Division of Human Rights on the Complaint of David G. Beatty vs AFTRA, 1975-1976 (Box 156, Folder 18)
  - Struthers, Sally vs Tandem Productions, Inc, 1975 (Box 156, Folder 19)
  - Stuart, Anna (incl. case vs Richard Astor Agency), 1973-1974 (Box 156, Folder 20)
  - Sweet Soul Music Bankruptcy, 1988 (Box 156, Folder 21)
  - Talent Agents: AFTRA vs Cogan, David J. Agency, Inc. re: Cogan, David J., 1987-1989 (Box 156, Folder 22)
  - Talent Agents: AFTRA vs Leaverton Associates, 1987 (Box 156, Folder 23)
  - Talent Agents: Artists' Managers Guild and Artists' Representatives Association, Inc. Agreements, 1943-1958 (Box 156, Folder 24)
  - Talent Agents: ATA Newsletters, 1988-1990 (Box 156, Folder 25)
  - Talent Agents: Association of Talent Agents vs AFTRA Legal Documents, 1990 (Box 156, Folder 26)
  - Talent Agents: Buchwald, Don & Associations, Inc. vs Robin Strasser and Benick Productions, Inc. re: Robin Strasser, 1987 (Box 156, Folder 27)
  - Talent Agents: Characters Agency, Nov 1988-Oct 1990 (Box 156, Folder 28)
  - Talent Agents: Characters Agency, Nov 1990-Dec 1990 (Box 156, Folder 29)
  - Talent Agents: Characters Agency, Jan 1991-Apr 1991 (Box 156, Folder 30)
  - Talent Agents: Characters Agency, May 1991-Nov 1991 (Box 156, Folder 31)
  - Talent Agents: Characters Agency Agreements, 1991 (Box 156, Folder 32)
  - Talent Agents: Cincinnati Agents Meeting, 1988 (Box 156, Folder 33)
  - Talent Agents: Complaint Against National Talent Associates, et al., 1974-1975 (Box 156, Folder 34)
  - Talent Agents: Correspondence and Related Material, 1982-1986 (Box 156, Folder 35)
  - Talent Agents: Correspondence and Related Material, 1987-1988 (Box 156, Folder 36)
  - Talent Agents: Correspondence and Related Material, 1989 (Box 156, Folder 37)
  - Talent Agents: Correspondence and Related Material, 1990 (Box 156, Folder 38)
  - Talent Agents: Department of Justice/AFTRA Agency Franchises, 1977 (Box 156, Folder 39)
  - Talent Agents: H.A. Artists vs AEA, 1980-1982 (Box 157, Folder 1)
  - Talent Agents: H.A. Artists vs AEA, 1978 (Box 157, Folder 2)
  - Talent Agents: H. A. Artists vs Richard Van Vleet re: Rule 12-B, 1984 (Box 157, Folder 3)
  - Talent Agents: Josephson, Marvin Associates vs Jimmie Walker; counterclaim Walker vs Josephson, 1978 (Box 157, Folder 4)
  - Talent Agents: Morris, William Agency, Inc. vs Forrest Sawyer re: Commission, 1985 (Box 157, Folder 5)
  - Talent Agents: Morris, William Agency, Inc. vs Forrest Sawyer re: Commission, 1988 (Box 157, Folder 6)
  - Talent Agents: National Agents Committee, 1969-1970 (Box 157, Folder 7)
  - Talent Agents: Negotiations, Correspondence and SAG Proposals, 1975 (Box 157, Folder 8)
  - Talent Agents: Rogers, Tristan vs Tyler Kjar Agency, 1984 (Box 157, Folder 9)
  - Talent Agents: Rule 12-B, Affidavit of Receipt of Proposed Changes, Feb 18, 1972 (Box 157, Folder 10)
  - Talent Agents: Rule 12-B, AFTRA Regulations Governing Agents, Jun 1, 1958 (Box 157, Folder 11)
  - Talent Agents: Rule 12-B Negotiations Attendance Sheets, 1972 (Box 157, Folder 12)
  - Talent Agents: Rule 12-B Negotiations Commission on Scale Petitions, Agencies A-F, 1972 (Box 157, Folder 13)
  - Talent Agents: Rule 12-B Negotiations Commission on Scale Petitions, Agencies H-R, 1972 (Box 157, Folder 14)
  - Talent Agents: Rule 12-B Negotiations Commission on Scale Petitions, Agencies S-W, 1972 (Box 157, Folder 15)
  - Talent Agents: Rule 12-B Negotiations Correspondence, Jan 1972-Mar 1972 (Box 157, Folder 16)
  - Talent Agents: Rule 12-B Negotiations Correspondence, Apr 1972-Sep 1972 (Box 157, Folder 17)
  - Talent Agents: SAG vs Tanya Blair Agency, 1979 (Box 157, Folder 18)
  - Talent Agents: Steele Agency a/k/a Take-One Talent re: Going into Chapter 7 Bankruptcy, 1989 (Box 157, Folder 19)
  - Talent Agents: Stone/Campbell Franchise Request, 1989 (Box 157, Folder 20)
  - Talent Agents: Talent Representatives, Inc. vs AFTRA, Jan 1982-May 1982 (Box 157, Folder 21)
  - Talent Agents: Talent Representatives, Inc. vs AFTRA, Copies of Correspondence re: Termination of Agency Franchise, 1984 (Box 157, Folder 22)
  - Talent Agents: Talent Representatives, Inc. vs AFTRA, Legal Documents, 1981 (Box 157, Folder 23)
  - Talent Agents: Talent Representatives, Inc. vs AFTRA, Legal Documents, Jun 1982-Dec 1982 (Box 157, Folder 24)
  - Talent Agents: Talent Representatives, Inc. vs AFTRA, Legal Documents, 1984 (Box 157, Folder 25)
  - Talent Agents: Talent Representatives, Inc. vs Screen Actors Guild, Inc., Legal Documents, 1981 (Box 157, Folder 26)
  - Talent Agents: Twentieth Century Artists vs Peggy McCay re: Commission Payments, 1987 (Box 157, Folder 27)